Iselin Haugen

I was born in Alta, Finnmark, but have spent most of my time south in Norway. I got two kids, a girl that is 10 years old and a boy who is 5 years old.



iselin@knuff.no



Front-End Development student

@ Noroff School of technology and digital media art

Aug. 2020 - Jun. 2022

Through school, I have really found the joy of coding. I have been challenged in a new way, experienced that errors can only be solved by logic. I get so happy when I achieve something - and so distressed when i don't. Coding is full of feelings. Dividing big problem into small tasks and solving them one by one.

We have been through a lot during our classes, not all in detail - but our teachers were good at pointing out what we needed to learn, and what was nice-to-know.

I've heard Per Harald Borgen onced said: "Motivation is by far the most important ingredient for learning how to code."

And luckily I have had a lot of motivation!

Relevant experience

Creative manager

@ UTD Reklameprodusenten

Aug. 2014 - Aug. 2020

Working as a creative manager, I was responsible for graphic production for a large customer group.

I have been a project manager on various project. Taken care of both designing and administrative tasks, and I've been a quality controller for all the bus decors in Vestfold and Buskerud. In addition to the academic aspect, this has given me good experience and knowledge on customer follow-up, structure and business in general.

Graphic designer

@ Vestfold Blad

2013

My main tasks was graphic layout and production of ads, brochures, logos, as well as overall design of customer's profile. In a way this was my first real graphic design job, with great colleagues who made me better and build a solid foundation for future jobs.

Visual Merchandiser / Assistant shop manager

2010 - 2012

@ Lindex AS

Through my position in Lindex I worked with profiling our store. But I also were involved with establishing new stores with exhibition podiums, window decor, floor-planning and campaigns. I've been in processes when hiring, managed work schedule for 13 employees and delegation of tasks.

Education

Front-End Development

@ Noroff, School of technology 2020 - 2022

Graphic Design

@ Norges Kreative Fagskole,Trondheim2007 - 2009

Skills

Design

InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, Adobe XD

Tools & Platforms

Git, Netlify, Heroku, Wordpress API, Strapi, Cloudinary

Programming Languages

JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, HTML, CSS/Sass, Styled Components

Interests

Gaming, fun facts, podcasts, fresh air, take-away, puzzles, drawing and being active.